var quiz = [{
  question: "Pavement's original drummer was:",
  answers: ['Gary Young', 'John Bonham', 'Neil Peart', 'Animal', 'Josh Freese'],
  correctAnswer: 0
}, {
  question: "The two principal members of Royal Trux went on to form all of the following bands except:",
  answers: ['The Howling Hex', 'Black Bananas', 'RTX', 'XTC', 'Hagerty-Toth Band'],
  correctAnswer: 3
}, {
  question: "Bill Callahan, aka Smog, wrote a zine by the name of:",
  answers: ['Disaster', 'Proclivity', 'Supper', 'Apocalypse', 'Forced Exposure'],
  correctAnswer: 0
}, {
  question: "Pacific Northwest record label Kill Rock Stars released albums by all the following except:",
  answers: ['Elliott Smith', 'Deerhoof', 'Bratmobile', 'Miranda July', 'Beat Happening'],
  correctAnswer: 4
}, {
  question: "Singer and guitarist Chan Marshall records and performs under the name:",
  answers: ['Witchypoo', 'Cat Power', 'Courtney Love', 'Flying Nun', 'Slim Moon'],
  correctAnswer: 1
}, {
  question: "Dale Crover has played drums for which of the following bands?",
  answers: ['Guided by Voices and R.E.M.', 'Palace Brothers and King Kong', 'Murder City Devils and Lungfish', 'Melvins and Nirvana', 'Sebadoh and Dinosaur Jr.'],
  correctAnswer: 3
}, {
  question: "Tortoise is from:",
  answers: ['Los Angeles', 'Phoenix', 'Chicago', 'Berlin', 'New Paltz'],
  correctAnswer: 2
}, {
  question: "The Elephant Six Collective included all of the following bands except:",
  answer: ['Olivia Tremor Control', 'Neutral Milk Hotel', 'Apples In Stereo', 'Elf Power', 'Superchunk'],
  correctAnswer: 4
}, {
  question: "Two members of Blonde Redhead are:",
  answer: ['Psychics', 'Twins', 'Attorneys', 'Sisters', 'Cousins'],
  correctAnswer: 1
}, {
  question: "Chris Lombardi is the founder of:",
  answer: ['Matador Records', 'Homestead Records', 'Drag City Records', 'DGC Records', 'Merge Records'],
  correctAnswer: 0
}
  ];

for (var i = 0; i <= quiz.length; i++) {
  
}


function barGraph(arr) {
  
}